Let us now move a little further.  Let's
talk to Napu about some more numbers.
HDFC AMC and Engine.  Tell me the name.
Absolutely.  You may see mixed results coming from HDFC AMC.
Here we are expecting 20% ​​growth in EUM.   If you
look at the core revenue, you will see 18% growth
coming here.  Operating profit may
also see a jump of 19%.  If we
look at profits, we have to keep an eye on core profits.  There can be a
growth of 17% there.
But the net profit may
see a decline.  Other
income is expected to decline
both quarter-on-quarter
as bond yields have
seen an increase and market returns have
also been weak.  And the reason for the 20%
growth in AUM will be the steady
inflows that the company has seen,
you will see its impact in the AUM.  However, the
company's EBITDA margins are expected to be around 80%
in quarter four.
Talking about jail one, Strong Quarter will be
seen coming here.  Revenue is
expected to grow by 33%.  Look at total income,
which includes other income.
Strong growth of around 34% can be seen there.
Ah, if we look at the profit before tax, the
company can register a profit of around Rs 400 crore.  And after
tax profit too,
growth of more than 65% can be seen in this quarter.  The
highlight will be the pre-day order
run rate which will be
seen improving quarter on quarter and also the
FNO volumes will be monitored on a viava basis.  At the same time, the
company's average MTF book will be
seen growing.  It is possible that it may
reach record levels, so there will be an
eye on that as well and the
market will also keep an eye on the customer auditions that have taken place in this quarter,
so the results will be good from
Angel One.